<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DelegateAdapters</string>
    <string name="item_video">Videos</string>
    <string name="item_photo">Photos</string>
    <string name="item_article">Articles</string>

    <string name="viewtype_cat3">
        13 Reasons To Love Black Cats\n
        1. Sometimes they just look like really cute fluffballs with eyes.\n
        2. They are basically miniature black panthers.\n
        3. They are natural models in the right lighting.\n
        4. They are hardly ~spooky~ when they are sleeping so sweetly.\n
        5. They are encouraging.\n
        6. And can be ever so patient.\n
        7. Any color looks good on them.\n
        8. When they are mischievous, it\'s utterly adorable.\n
        9. They are really great confidants.
        10. Their fur is SO. DANG. SILKY.\n
        11. And their yellow eyes stand out MAGNIFICENTLY against their black fur.\n
        12. Or maybe they have two different colored eyes, in which case they are EVEN MORE MAGNIFICENT.\n
        13. You can take super ~artsy~ black and white photos of them.\n </string>

    <string name="viewtype_dog2">
        Alaskan Malamute\n
        No doubt about it, the Alaskan Malamute is a beautiful breed, but what makes the Malamute different than the Siberian Husky? What\’s it\’s story?
        Well, if you’ve ever been confused, curious, or just in love with the Alaskan Malamute, these fun facts are for you. \n
        1. The Alaskan Malamute was officially recognized by the American Kennel Club in 1935. \n
        2. But their true origin far predates that—the breed is over thousands of years old. \n
        3. An early version of the Malamute is said to have accompanied Siberian nomads across the Bering straits into what is now known as Alaska. \n
        4. Those nomads were called Mahlemuts, which is where the breed gets its name. \n
        5. The dog came to be a cornerstone of Inuit life for hundreds of years. They were used to hunt seals, chase away polar bears, and sled dogs. \n </string>
</resources>
